(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-09T02:24:57.256252",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
はーい注目 まaidっちょ踊ってこうか？
Hey, attention! Shall we dance once more?
視線牛耳ってんのは…
Stealing everyone's gaze...
あ・あ・あい
Ah-ah-aye!
あれ～？君たちの声 まだ足りてないんじゃないの～？
Huh~? Are your voices still not enough~?
our night's just begun aye let's blast it!
赤く火照るface
A flushed, burning face
ヒートアップしちゃって絡むsweat
Heating up and tangling sweat
渇いた咽潤す オアシスよマリンブルー
Moistening a dry throat, an oasis of marine blue
あっはーん！たまらないでしょ？
Ah-ha! Isn't it irresistible?
（ぱっきゅん♡）
(Bang-kyun♡)
from shore to shore my moves bring the storm to the floor
thunder rays blast a sonic boom
i ride the beat like i'm surfing shock waves
don't need no sunblock
i can make it rain 'cause you hit the jackpot
baby get ready if you wanna ride on with the ogs
アーウチチな二人はだあれ？
Who are those scorching hot pair?
(yeah baby)
Hands up ぶち上げたまえ！
Hands up, put 'em in the air!
(oh baby)
クラッときちゃう様な熱が足りない
There's not enough heat to make you dizzy
our night's just begun aye let's blast it!
ハジけて派手にいったーれ！
Break loose and go all out with a bang!
(yeah baby)
来世まで we wanna party
Until the afterlife, we wanna party
all eyes on me i can taste the high
Aye まだまだ沸いてこうぜ
Aye, keep the hype going!
はーい注目 まaidっちょ踊ってこうか？
Hey, attention! Shall we dance once more?
視線牛耳ってんのは…
Stealing everyone's gaze...
あ・あ・あい
Ah-ah-aye!
よそ見しちゃやーん♡
Don't look away♡
マリンがbestest girlじゃん？
Isn't Marine the bestest girl?
砂の数よりも魅力がある キミたちもね、虜でしょ？
More charming than sand. You guys are captivated too, right?
は？年の数って誰が言った？
Huh? Who said anything about my age?
（うふん♡）大人の魅力よっっておいゴラァ！
(Ufun♡) It's mature charm—hey, you punk!
マリンは17たいっておいきけや！！
Marine is 17, I said, listen up!!
我慢の限界かな とかって、きゅ♡
Is this the limit of my patience, or something? Kyu♡
bring in the heat that can't be splashed away
fishing a big catch the stardom i deserve
but i'm just chilling a mocktail maitai sipping
'cause i got that juice might let you have a taste
見てこのbody マネでしょ、honey
Look at this body, money, right, honey?
秘な素肌ね
Such secret bare skin.
やん！見ないで、待って
Yikes! Don't look, wait—
beside a bonfire our luring smoke takes you higher
ね？We drive you crazy
Right? We drive you crazy
熱苦しくなってこう もうどうしようもない
Let's get fired up, there's no turning back now
my bright spotlight
どんどん新境地いっちゃいそ？
Shall we dive right into brand new territory?
(oh baby)
アーウチチな二人はだあれ？
Who are those scorching hot pair?
(yeah baby)
Hands up ぶち上げたまえ！
Hands up, put 'em in the air!
(oh baby)
クラッときちゃう様な熱が足りない
There's not enough heat to make you dizzy
our night's just begun aye let's blast it!
ハジけて派手にいったーれ！
Break loose and go all out with a bang!
(yeah baby)
来世まで we wanna party
Until the afterlife, we wanna party
Aye まだまだ沸いていこうぜ
Aye, let's keep the hype going!
はーい注目 まあ いっちょ踊ってこうか？
Hey everyone, shall we dance one more time?
視線牛耳ってんのは…
Stealing all the gazes...
Let's hit it
アタシたちマジで最強じゃん？
Aren't we seriously the strongest?
Just two besties so fly!
Ah-ah-ah
本当は分かっていた いけないことだって分かっていたのに
To be honest, I knew, even though I knew it was wrong,
この手をすり抜ける全部が愛に見えたの
everything that slipped through these hands looked like love.
確かめていた言葉が形になって、揺れるだけ
The words I made sure of take shape, only wavering.
弾いて、描いて、きっと、それだけ
Strumming, drawing, surely, just that.
つまらないな、正解の読み合わせ
Isn't it boring, comparing answers?
あとちょっとで分かりかけていたのに
Even though I was so close to figuring it out.
飲んで、吐いて全部忘れちゃえ
Drinking, vomiting, forgetting everything.
水をまとった本心と鏡合わせ
My true feelings clad in water in the mirror.
見つめ、会えたら
Once our eyes meet...
Overdose 君とふたり やるせない日々
Overdose, you and me, days of helplessness.
解像度の悪い夢を見たい
I wanna dream of a blurred-out nightmare.
Overdose 君とふたり 甘いハッタリ
Overdose, you and me, a sweet bluff.
Don't stop it music, darling
本当に分かっている？ いけないことだって分かっている？
Do you really know? Do you know it's wrong?
多分、時間だけが過ぎていく 問答で満ちていく
Maybe time's just passing, filled with Q&A.
言い訳する間もなく、裸になってしまうだけ
With no time to make excuses, I'll just go naked.
きっと、溜まっていくんだ ずっと 終わってしまえばいいと、ふっと
Surely, it'll pile up forever, wishing it'd just end.
爛れて腐っていく、あの甘い果実のようにぽんと放れていく
Rotting like sweet fruit, we break apart.
だから、踊って、眠って 全部忘れちゃえ
That's why I dance, sleep, and forget it all.
嘘を被ったあなたと隣り合わせ
Side by side with you, draped in lies.
見つめ、会えたら
Once our eyes meet...
Overdose 君とふたり 分かりたいのに
Overdose, you and me, wanting to understand,
変に間の悪い嘘が嫌い
but I hate those awkwardly timed lies.
Overdose 君とふたり 分かりたいのに
Overdose, you and me, wanting to understand,
Two step from (hell) with me, darling
Overdose 君とふたり やるせない日々
Overdose, you and me, days of helplessness.
解像度の悪い夢を見たい
I wanna dream of a blurred-out nightmare.
Overdose 君とふたり 甘いハッタリ
Overdose, you and me, a sweet bluff.
Don't stop it music, darling
Overdose 君とふたり 分からないけど、
Overdose, you and me, though I don't know,
変に間の悪い嘘でもいいから
even awkwardly timed lies are fine, so
どう、君とふたり 甘いハッタリ
what do you think, you and me, a sweet bluff?
Don't stop it music, darling
愛包ダンスホール 今日はボレロ
Love-hug dance hall, today is a bolero.
ろくでなし少年 甘酸っぱい感情
Good-for-nothing boy, bittersweet emotions.
人類満杯 ワイワイバイバイ
Humanity overflowing, yay-yay bye-bye.
オープントースターは漏れ漏れよ
The open toaster is leaking everywhere.
おかわりはアンコール次次第ね
Seconds depend on the encore.
オワラナイ・ラブコール・ノ・ダンス・デ
In this unending love call dance!
愛包ダンスホール
Love-hug dance hall!
おかわりならもっと欲しい
If it's seconds, I want more.
愛包ダンスホール
Love-hug dance hall!
3.1415926535のπだって
Even pi is 3.1415926535...
割り切れない気持ち抱えてるよ
Holding feelings that can't be divided.
ロボも幻人も猿も円陣組んで仲良くやれたらとて
If robots, phantoms, and apes formed a circle...
割り切れない命いっそガイのヘブン
An un-divisible life in Gaia's heaven.
今夜はいいんじゃない？ ほらオエオエオエオよ
Isn't tonight fine? Come on, oe-oe-oe-oe!
踊ればいいんじゃない？ ほらフリフリフラレバ
Shouldn't we dance? Come on, furi-furi-furareba!
休戦しようぜ 涙腺が源泉温泉
Let's call a truce, tear ducts acting like hot springs.
汗ばんだらガンダラサンサラ
Once we sweat, Gandhara Samsara!
高まった感動の再会 集まった愛情のWi-Fi
Heightened emotional reunion, gathered Wi-Fi of love.
街よって常燈の人提灯 愛してるが重なって
Lanterns of the street, love piling up,
集まった人類の状態
the state of gathered humanity.
熱いミートパイみたいだね
It's like a hot meat pie, isn't it?
パパッパッパッパ パパイ！？
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa pie!?
愛包！愛一杯で惚れ惚れよ
Aipai! Fall hopelessly in love with all my love!
蕩けた少年 甘酸っぱい感情
A melted boy, bittersweet feelings
求愛人類♥︎満杯だい
A mankind full of courtship ♥︎
完敗！完全に惚れ惚れよ
Total defeat! Fall completely, hopelessly in love
ミルフィーユみたいね愛の踊り
Like a mille-feuille, a dance of love
頭んなかパッパラパッパー
Parapa-pa-pa in my head!
艶やかなルールのジョンレノンも愛好家
Even John Lennon of the glamorous rules is a fan
イマジン・オール・ザ・ピーパーの最善でダンスホールじゃ歌姫もヒーロー
At the best of Imagine All the People, even the diva is a hero in the dance hall
乾杯！今日はボレロ
Cheers! Today is Bolero
交わって人類 馬鹿になって笑って おかわり欲しいでしょ？
Intertwining humanity, acting silly and laughing, you want seconds, don't you?
全人類公正舞踏会の目指すべき一日は
The day that the All-Humanity Fair Ball should aim for is
レンジでチンしてパイになる様な
Like something popped in the microwave to become a pie
脳みそもトロトロの世の実現をスローガンにオールナイト
All-night with the slogan of realizing a world where even brains are melting
踊りましてボン・ボヤージュ！
Dancing, bon voyage!
つきまして聖人を座座
Whereupon, sitting like saints
パパッパッパッパ パパイ！ 人類最高のダンスタイム
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa pie! Humanity's best dance time
愛包ダンスホール 鳴呼ライライ愛包ダンスホール
Aipai Dance Hall, ah, rairai Aipai Dance Hall
愛包ダンスホール
Aipai Dance Hall
僕等が生まれて初めて知る音は心臓の鼓動だろ
The first sound we know since we were born is the heartbeat, right?
トトン トトン タトン タトン タテン タトンタ
Toton toton taton taton taten tatonta
それはリズムと知った
I learned that it was rhythm
いにしえも 今ドキも
Both in ancient times and nowadays
♥︎BEATが僕達を包んで繋いでんだろ？
♥︎The BEAT is wrapping and connecting us, right?
パパッパッパッパ パパイ！？
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa pie!?
愛包！愛一杯で惚れ惚れよ
Aipai! Fall hopelessly in love with all my love!
蕩けた少年 甘酸っぱい感情
A melted boy, bittersweet feelings
求愛人類♥︎満杯だい
A mankind full of courtship ♥︎
完敗！完全に惚れ惚れよ
Total defeat! Fall completely, hopelessly in love
ミルフィーユみたいね愛の踊り
Like a mille-feuille, a dance of love
頭んなかパッパラパッパー
Parapa-pa-pa in my head!
ラララララララララララ まるでバージンロードで踊ってるみたい
Lalalalalalalalala, like dancing down the virgin road
生まれ変わった様な気分でして
Feeling like I've been reborn
乾杯！今日はボレロ
Cheers! Today is Bolero
交わって人類 馬鹿になって笑って てってってっ照れてってー
Intertwining humanity, acting silly and laughing, blushing and being shy...
寂しいよな 終わりは近づくけどさ
It's kind of lonely, though the end is approaching
終わらない様の様に続けりゃいい
We might as well keep going like it never ends
計算なんてできないが…！
Though we can't calculate...!
愛いっぱい！愛包ダンスホール 今日はボレロ
Full of love! Aipai Dance Hall, today is Bolero
蕩けた少年 甘酸っぱい感情
A melted boy, bittersweet feelings
求愛人類♥︎満杯だい
A mankind full of courtship ♥︎
また食べに来てね あなたならいつでもいいよ
Come eat again, anytime is fine for you
おかわり欲しいでしょ？
You want seconds, don't you?
愛包ダンスホール
Aipai Dance Hall
おかわりならばもっと欲しい
If it's seconds, I want more
愛包ダンスホール どうぞ
Aipai Dance Hall, here you go
いなせだね 夏を連れて来た女
She's stylish, a woman who brought summer with her
渚まで噂走るよ めっ！
Rumors run all the way to the beach, mey!
涼気な目もと流し目 eye eye eye
Cool glances, flirtatious looks, eye eye eye
粋な事件 起こりそうだぜ めっ！
Something stylish is about to happen, mey!
妖しい Sweet Baby め組のひとだね
Mysterious Sweet Baby, you're a member of the Megumi clan
お前のニュースで ビーチは突然 パニック
At your news, the beach is suddenly in panic
Baby, baby, be my girl 夢中なのさ be my girl
Baby, baby, be my girl, I'm entranced, be my girl
浮気な微笑みに 他たち気もそぞろ
Your fickle smile leaves others distracted
男たちの心 奪うたびに お前 綺麗になってくね…
Every time you steal men's hearts, you grow more beautiful...
夏の罪は素敵すぎる
The sins of summer are too wonderful
いなせだね 夏を連れて来た女
She's stylish, a woman who brought summer with her
渚まで噂走るよ めっ！
Rumors run all the way to the beach, mey!
涼気な目もと流し目 eye eye eye
Cool glances, flirtatious looks, eye eye eye
粋な事件 起こりそうだぜ めっ！
Something stylish is about to happen, mey!
小粋だね 髪に飾った花も 細い腰 あわせ揺れるよ めっ！
Stylish, the flower in your hair too, your slender waist sways along, mey!
ひと夏の恋を引き込む eye eye eye
Pulling in the love of a summer, eye eye eye
気まぐれに片目閉じるよ めっ！
You wink whimsically with one eye, mey!
夏に繰り出した め組の人だね
You're a woman of the Megumi group who ventured out into summer,
今年はお前が 渚きってのアイドル
this year, you're the top idol of the beach!
Baby, baby, be my girl 抱きしめたい by my girl
Baby, baby, be my girl, I want to hold you close, be my girl.
お前が微笑めば すべてが上の空
When you smile, everything fades away.
男たちの心 奪うたびにお前
Every time you steal men's hearts,
綺麗になってくね…
You become more and more beautiful...
夏の罪は 素敵すぎる
Summer sins are far too wonderful!
いなせだね 夏を連れて来た女
You're so stylish, a woman who brought summer,
渚まで噂走るよ めっ！
Rumors run all the way to the beach, hey!
涼し気な目元流し目 eye eye eye
Cool eyes, sidelong glances, eye eye eye,
粋な事件 起こりそうだぜ めっ！
A stylish incident is about to happen, hey!
なんと！姫森ルーナさんが来て下さえました！ありがとうございます！
What! Himemori Luna-san came to join us! Thank you so much!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
お邪魔しまーす！
Pardon the interruption!
はい、おめでとうおめでとう！
Yes, congratulations, congratulations!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
ということでね、もう今日は姫森ルーナさんと行ったっていうこの「め組のひと」ダンスホールをですね、3人で歌っちゃいました！
So today, the three of us got to sing "Megumi no Hito" dance hall version with Himemori Luna-san!
イェーイ！イェーイ！最高！
Yay! Yay! Awesome!
3人バージョンめっちゃめちゃ楽しい！めっちゃ可愛くなっててもうすごい嬉しかったんですけども
The 3-person version is super fun! It got super cute and I was so happy, but
船長的に、さ、一番最初ね、この曲選んでパート分け作ったときに、もう、なんか、え、待ってマリンがノイズすぎるとと思って
From the Captain's perspective, right at the beginning when I chose this song and made the part breakdown, I thought, wait, Marine is too noisy—
なんでやねん！
Why's that?!
めっちゃパート少なくしてたんですよ。
I made my parts super few.
そうなんだ！
Is that so!
びとも、サビとかこれ全部ね、姫森ルーナさんに歌ってほしいと…
Even the choruses and everything, I wanted Himemori Luna-san to sing...
いやいやいや、マリンが歌っちゃダメだと思って
No no no, I thought Marine shouldn't sing it,
自分の自分のライブなのになぜか姫森ルーナさんだらけの状態にしてたら、姫森ルーナさんサイドから「いやこのまりさんのパートを増やしてくれと」
even though it's my own live, I made it full of Himemori Luna-san, and then Luna-san's side said, "No, please increase Mari-san's parts!"
主役ですから！
Because you're the star!
そう、そう！自分の声欲しくないから
Yeah, yeah! Because I don't want much of my voice,
1回歌わしていただきましたでもすごい一緒に歌えて楽しかったですありがとうございました！
I got to sing it once, but it was so fun singing together, thank you!
ありがとうございます！え、ハーフバージョンもね3人バージョンにさせていただいて
Thank you! And we made the half version into a 3-person version too,
のためのねそうありがたい
for that reason, so thank you.
練習して可愛くなりました！
We practiced and it became cute!
ありがとうございます！嬉しい本当に嬉しいです！
Thank you! I'm so happy, truly happy!
もう生でこの歌声が聴けたことがもう感動こちらこそです！本当だよ！
Being able to live-hear this singing voice is so touching, same here! It's true!
めちゃくちゃ楽しかった！いっぱいいっぱい歌えて踊ってもらっても最高ですよ！
It was super fun! Singing so much and having you dance, it's the best!
ありがとうございます！もう1曲がね「め組の人」なんですけど、これなんで選んだと思いますか？
Thank you! The other song is "Megumi no Hito", why do you think I chose this?
え？なんで？みんなで、たくさん…
Eh? Why? Everyone, a lot...
こう歌謡曲が好きだからみたいな。そうなんですけど、あの、この「め組の人」って、あのこうだくみさんのバージョンがあるんですけど
Because I like kayokyoku like this. That's true, but, um, this "Megumi no Hito", there's Koda Kumi-san's version,
今日このそのキーなんですけど、なんか、その、キー聞いてる時にね
and today's key is that, but when listening to that key,
あ、これ、ひめひなさん、めっじゃう、これ本当？半分こうだくみあんと…
Ah, this, Himehina-san, match, is this true? Half Koda Kumi-an and...
そう、それ多いよ！と思って絶対合うと思って、あの3人で歌ったら熱いかなと思ってお願いさせていただきました！
Yeah, so many! I thought it would definitely match, and I thought it would be hot if the three of us sang it, so I asked!
めちゃめちゃ楽しかった！めっちゃ、そう、え、歌いやすかったんじゃないですか？
It was super fun! Super, right, eh, wasn't it easy to sing?
めっちゃあってたからめっちゃ良かった！そうそうそう！
Because it matched so well, it was great! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
めっちゃもう本当声のシナジー合って歌いやすかっただろうなと思って
I thought our voices had great synergy and it must have been easy to sing,
すごい微差だった何度もね繰り返し聞いていただきたいなと思います！ぜひ！
and it was wonderful, I hope people listen to it repeatedly! Please!
ええ、ひなも聴こう！え、地味に、今日、初絡みなのです！
Eh, Hina will listen too! Um, secretly, today is our first interaction!
そうなんだ！初めてなんだの！
Is that so! It's the first time!
実は、ちょっとあの、時系列的に、もう、あの、お邪魔してる姫森ルーナさんチャンネルにお邪魔したあとになってるんですけど
Actually, chronologically, this is after I appeared on Himemori Luna-san's channel,
ここが初絡みなのですよ！そう！今日初めて！
but here is our first interaction! Yeah! Today for the first time!
初めまして！初めまして！初めまして！
Nice to meet you! Nice to meet you! Nice to meet you!
もうなんか、すごい、全然、もう、全然まだドキドキモードが抜けてなくて
And somehow, I'm still all nervous and haven't shaken off the nervous mode,
すみません、なんか、なんかさっき「おまえ」って感じで言ってきてほしいって言われたけど、いけないいけない！
sorry, someone earlier asked me to say "omae" to them, but no way, no way!
あ、パンチ！やるか！パンチ！
Ah, punch! Shall we do it? Punch!
やるか！一緒にね！一生懸命戦ってますから！
Shall we do it? Together! We're fighting hard!
いや、ありがとうございます！え、これからもぜひ一緒にね、歌ったりなんだりんだりしたいな！
Well, thank you! Um, I definitely want to sing and do things together from now on!
それいいだね！もっとコラボしたいな！したいしましょう！しましょう、しましょう、しましょう！
That's great! I want to collaborate more! Let's do it! Let's do it, let's do it, let's do it!
なんかほらさ、動画でなんかやりたい！やりましょうよ！私大好きだから！
Like, hey, I want to do something in a video! Let's do it! Because I love it!
ああ、大好き！ひめひなの曲ももう超好き！え、ありがとうございます！
Ah, I love it! I super love Himehina's songs too! Eh, thank you!
え、ちょっと待ってでも、マリンがここに挟まったら処刑されちゃうって…
Eh, wait a minute, but if Marine gets caught in the middle here, I'll get executed—
なんで？！挟ま挟もうよ！
Why?! Let's sandwich [her]!
もうなんか顔のでかさが ちょっと待って。こう引いてと…イェーイ！
My face looks big—wait, pulling back like this... Yay!
ひなのフレーム！ひなのフレーム！
Hina's frame! Hina's frame!
可愛い！あ、最高、最高！ありがとうございます！
Cute! Ah, awesome, awesome! Thank you!
スクショ、スクショ撮って、撮ってください！いい感じ！超可愛い！
Take a screenshot, take a screenshot! Looking good! Super cute!
え、カメラのアングルすごい！いい！
Eh, the camera angle is amazing! Great!
せーのは次の曲行きたいと思います。
We're going to move on to the next song.
行きますよ。
Here we go!
せーの！やった！やった！できた！
Ready, go! Yay! Yay! We did it!
いつか観ていた映画の中みたい
Just like in a movie I watched one day,
工事中の駅前 空へ背伸びしていくビルディング
skyscrapers under construction by the station stretch toward the sky.
ヒールが鳴らすリズムと命の音が揃う
The rhythm of my heels matches the sound of life.
あたしはまだ未完成で不完全
I'm still unfinished and imperfect.
起死回生のハウトゥー 知ってるの
I know how to make a miraculous comeback!
今が一番若いの 第六感、第六感たがって
Right now is my youngest! My sixth sense, my sixth sense—
今日は年甲斐ないことしたいの
today I want to do something unfitting for my age.
予定にないこと 第六感、第六感おしえて 物足りないの
Teach me something unexpected, sixth sense! I'm not satisfied—
引き合いたいよ 偶然とハートしたい
I want us to connect, I want a chance encounter!
さぁおいでませ誰彼 (I got it)
Come one, come all, (I got it)
道連れ世は情け (I got it)
misery loves company, (I got it)
ご覧ましませこの手立て
feast your eyes on this strategy.
弱さ凌ぐ一手 賢さにあり
Overcoming weakness lies in cleverness.
いつか話した予想とは違っているものさ
It's different from what we talked about before,
そんな悲しまないでいいよ
but you don't need to be so sad about it.
今が一番早いの 第六感、第六感あやかって
Right now is the fastest! Riding on my sixth sense—
疾走るハート嘘はつけないよ
a racing heart cannot tell lies.
台詞ない言葉 交換、交換おしえて そうくだらないを
Teach me wordless exchanges, let's share the nonsense!
言い合いたい 特別を感じたい
I want to speak our minds, I want to feel special.
産声があげた日は理由もなく泣いていたのに
Even though on the day I was born I cried for no reason,
今僕ら泣くことすらうまくできずに
now we can't even cry properly anymore.
されどしかと死守せよ 品格と真似できぬプライドを
Still, firmly guard your dignity and irreplaceable pride!
せーので手放せよ 感覚で胸を打つものそれ以外を
Let them go all at once—anything other than what strikes the heart by instinct!
Crazy about this thing.
今が一番若いの 第六感、第六感たがって
Right now is my youngest! My sixth sense, my sixth sense—
今日は年甲斐ないことしたいの
today I want to do something unfitting for my age.
予定にないこと 第六感、第六感おしえて おしえて、おしえて
Teach me something unexpected, sixth sense! Tell me, tell me!
今最高潮なんです！第六感、第六感たがって
Right now we're at our peak! My sixth sense, my sixth sense—
このまま何処までいけるの
how far can we go just like this?
途方もないままで第六感、第六感おしえて
Without knowing where it leads, sixth sense, sixth sense, tell me—
もう揺るがないこの速度は そう偶然とハートしたい
this unwavering speed is a chance encounter with the heart!
魅惑を隠箱 秘宝に香る危なげな Dangerous Marine Smell
A box hiding allure, fragrant and perilous treasure. Dangerous Marine Smell.
♥Ahoy♥
(これ開けたら君たちになってってあげるべきかな…？)
(If I open this, what should I say to you all...?)
「探してたのは歌手のお・ん・な？でしょ？」
"Were you looking for a sin-gin' la-dy...?"
「あぁん♥そんなにがついちゃダメだゾ♥かな？」
"Ahhn♥ Don't get too greedy on me, okay?♥"
「お宝より魅力的な”モノ”見つけちゃった…？いいじゃない♥」
"Did you find something 'more attractive' than treasure...? Isn't that nice?♥"
誘うガーネットの赤 極上の海賊の秘宝 それは私
The inviting garnet red, the ultimate pirate's treasure—that is me.
艶が溢れ漂う香りをどうか怖がってみて開けてみて
Please don't be afraid of the overflowing, alluring scent—try opening it.
(アッハッハッ…♥)
(Ah-ha-ha...♥)
Sexy世界一 Superピチピチ ぶっちゃけ船長捕まえたいくない？
The world's sexiest, super fresh! Honestly, don't you want to capture the captain?
魅惑を隠す箱 秘宝に香る危険な
A bewitching box hiding secrets, a dangerous fragrance
誘うガーネットの赤 極上の海賊の秘宝
Dyed in garnet red, the ultimate pirate's treasure
それは私 艶が溢れ漂う
That is me, overflowing with alluring charm
香りをどうかせんがないで
Don't fear this scent, and open it up
(Ah-hoy!! DA-BA-DA-BOI)
秘宝の鍵を
The key to the secret treasure...
(Ah-hoy!! DA-BA-DA-BOI)
優しく刺して
Pierce me gently...
(Ah-hoy!! DA-BA-DA-BOI)
宝庫の扉 マジで早く開けて
The door to the vault, seriously open it quickly!
♡Ahoy♡
じれったい貴方の手 海図にこぼす甘いため息のTease
Your impatient hand, a sweet sigh spilled on the chart... Tease
純紅のバラが しおれる前に
Before the crimson rose withers away,
WE WILL SAIL THE SEVEN SEAS
(七つの大海を)
(The seven seas)
SUMMER SUN SMILING WITH GLEE
(股にかけ進め)
(Sail forth across the seas)
SHINING OCEAN OF MARINE
(股ってワードからなに想像してんの)
(What are you imagining with a word like that?)
Now please grant my dearest dream
OPEN UP THIS BOX
OPEN IT RIGHT NOW OR I WILL SCREAM
(さもなきゃ)
(Or else...)
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!!!!!! (あけろおおおおおお)
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!!!!!! (Open it up!!!!!!)
泣く子も黙る Naughty 脳殺ビーム
Naughty mind-control beam that silences crying kids,
キミたちもう我慢できないくない？ (KABOOM...)
Can you guys really not hold back anymore? (KABOOM...)
You're gonna own the pleasure Maybe love of me?
私の全てを手に入れて
Get your hands on my everything...
(Ah-hoy!! DA-BA-DA-BOI)
金銀財宝
Gold and silver treasures
(Ah-hoy!! DA-BA-DA-BOI)
はした金でしょ
Are just pocket change, right?
(Ah-hoy!! DA-BA-DA-BOI)
しわしわになっちゃう
You'll end up all wrinkled!
誰か助けて
Somebody help me!
マジで遠慮すぎ キミたち何考えてんの
Seriously, you're holding back too much, what are you thinking?
分かってんだろ 渇望
You know what you crave,
だから今すぐ開けてよ 宝箱
So open it right now, the treasure box!
あなたを待つガーネット…
The garnet waiting for you...
(キミ…キミたち…開けて～!!)
(You... You guys... Open it up~!!)
はーい！ レオル、あっ、待って、違う。歌手の女
Hii! Reol— ah, wait, no. The female singer—
歌手の女、歌手の女、歌手の女です！
The female singer, the female singer, I'm the female singer!
歌手の女、ありがとうございます！
Female singer, thank you very much!
お誕生日おめでとうございます！ 今日誕生日なんです！
Happy birthday! Today is my birthday!
はい！え？え？
Yes! Eh? Eh?
おい、今日も生むなよ！
Hey, don't give birth today either!
違う、なんか想定では、レオルからこう誕生日トークが来る
No, like, in the plan, Reol was supposed to bring up a birthday talk...
ああ、なるほど。想定だったけど。
Ah, I see. Even though it was planned.
でも、お誕生日については触れられないえないですか？
But, can't we touch upon the birthday?
え、なぜですか？触れてくださいよ、全然。
Eh, why? Please talk about it, absolutely.
育成になったんですか？
Did you evolve?
あ、そこですか？もちろん、17歳ごしゅ……6しゅごしゅごしゅう……どっちだ？ご……5から6週の間です。
Ah, that place? Of course, 17 years old, 5 weeks... 6 weeks... 5 weeks... which is it? Between 5 and 6 weeks.
なるほど。
I see.
はい。あんまり計算はしないで貰った方が。
Yes. It's better not to calculate too much.
一応ね、この「歌手の女」とね、マリンはね、何年、どれぐらい何年ぐらいですかね？
Anyway, as for this "female singer" and Marine, how many years, about how many years has it been?
3年前ぐらい？ 3、4年前ぐらい？
About 3 years ago? About 3 or 4 years ago?
3、4年前ぐらいに、え、何？あ、関係値？
About 3 or 4 years ago, in, what? Ah, our relationship?
あ、関係値関係値。関係値は、まあ、でも、ね、あの、海賊のコスプレをし始めぐらいからじゃないですか？
Ah, relationship, relationship. Our relationship is, well, around when you started doing pirate cosplays, right?
そうですね、海賊のコスプレをし始めたこともありました。
That's right, there was a time I started doing pirate cosplays.
今やこんな大きな船に。
And now on such a big ship.
ええ、そう、まあこれちょっと今日レンタル船ということで。
Yeah, well, this is a rental ship for today.
リースなんだ。
It's a lease.
基本自分の船、夢を見せていけよ。
Basically your own ship, show us your dreams!
おい、誕生日らい、誕生日ぐらいね、もらった設定なんでね。
Hey, since it's my birthday, I was given this setting.
ね、誕生日プレゼントもステキステキな、あ、ありがとうございます。そんな場所に呼んでいただいて。
Right, birthday presents are wonderful, ah, thank you very much for inviting me to such a place.
ありがとうございます。今日ね、この2曲歌ったんですけど、ちょっとね。
Thank you very much. Today, you know, we sang these two songs, but you know...
なんか何歌うか一緒にいろいろ考えて、なんか、マリンの持ち歌と、レオルの持ち歌をそれぞれ歌いたいよねって話になり。
We thought about what to sing together, and talked about how we each wanted to sing Marine's songs and Reol's songs respectively.
で、マリバコを選んだのは、もう絶対、レオルのこの「歌手の女」としての、歌手の女ぜんとして、この、この歌を、歌手の女ぜんとして、そう、この歌唱力を、見せつけるには絶対これがいいと思って選んだんですが、結果、なんかマリンが処刑される羽目になっちゃった。
And, why I chose Maribako was because I definitely thought this was best to showcase Reol's vocal ability as the "female singer", as the ultimate female singer... but as a result, Marine ended up getting executed.
いやいやいや、すごかった、素晴ら
No no no, it was amazing, wonderful...
いや、やっぱりこれ、ね、かな……
Well, after all, this... right?
あ、そうそうそう。あそこはもうセクシー、ありがとう、ありがとうございます、セクシーにやっていただいて
Ah, right, right. That part was so sexy—thank you for doing it so sexy.
はい、ありがとうございます
Yes, thank you very much.
でね、第6巻もね、選ばさせていただきましたが！
And you know, we also chose Volume 6!
元々ね、あの、おちんと悩んだんだよね
Originally, you know, we were debating about "Ochin."
そう、ギガンティックを歌ってほしいっていうオーダーを私はしたんですけど
Right, I put in a request asking you to sing "Gigantic OTN."
で、ウロが歌ってほしいって言って
And Uro said she wanted me to sing it,
で、やっぱマリンはおちんでしょって、ふっくらじゃんおっぱいが
and said Marine is definitely Ochin, since your boobs are so plump!
って歌ってくれるのか！って思ったけど
I thought, "Will you really sing it?" But...
歌手のこの歌手としての全盛としたところを見せるなら第6巻のがいい
to show off her full prowess as a singer, Volume 6 is better!
そうですね、結局そっちになっちゃったですね
That's right, so it ended up being that one.
宣伝まで！衣装かっこよかったなと思います
Including promotion! I think the outfit was really cool.
今日ちょっと、あ、一味、あ、衣装が、一味っぽさ、一味っぽさっていうか、あの、まあ、あれです
Today, the outfit has that "Ichimi" vibe, or rather...
衣装、衣装ね、マリン船長の部下っぽさ
The outfit has a Marine Captain's subordinate vibe.
青い、あの青いんですけど
It's blue, well, it's blue, but...
あ、じゃねえよ！すいませんけど、部下っぽさとか言って、なんも、何にも部下っぽくないし青いし
Ah, wait, no! Sorry, I said subordinate vibe, but it's nothing like a subordinate, it's just blue!
青い、青いですね。ちょっと後でサイリウム買います
It's blue, it's blue. I'll buy some glow sticks later.
赤いから赤ね、赤ね、赤ね。すいません
Red means red, red, red. Sorry.
ま、まあまあ、でもね、すごい楽しかったですね
Well, anyway, it was a lot of fun.
いや、楽しかった、ありがとうございました
Yeah, it was fun, thank you very much!
またもし機会があったら一緒に歌いたいなと
If we get the chance again, I'd love to sing together.
いやもうこちらこそ、今度は私の船にも来てくだされ
Yes, absolutely, come aboard my ship next time!
マジで？呼ばれる？大丈夫かな？今から
Seriously? You're inviting me? Will I be okay?
お金貯めます。お前もレンタルすんだから
I'll start saving money now. You're renting yourself out too!
はい、ということでね、じゃあそんな感じで、まだまだ生誕祭続いていきますので、応援よろしくお願いしますね
So with that, the birthday celebration continues, so please keep supporting us!
楽しんでいってください、コメントしろよな
Enjoy yourselves, and leave comments!
なんだ急に！コメントしてくれよな。どこ目線の？部下、部下目線の、やっぱり。一緒に盛り上げてください！
What was that suddenly! Please leave comments from a subordinate's perspective. Let's get hyped together!
それでは、次の曲いって、み、み、いきます
Well then, let's go to the next song...
いこう！大丈夫か？大丈夫か？
Are you okay? Are you okay?
ちゅうか！ よっしゃらー！ありがとう！
Chuka! Yoshara! Thank you!
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
I won't let the romance scandal get away.
消してあげる
I'll make it disappear.
宣誓! 私が大統領になったら
Oath! When I'm president...
人の男にちょっかいかける女は島流しにします
I'll throw any woman who messes with another man off the island.
宣誓! 私が大統領になったら
Oath! When I'm president...
いやただの友達だよって誤魔化す奴へんから電流を流します
I'll electrify anyone who says, "No, we're just friends!"
だ・だ・だ・だ 大胆不敵 センセーショナルクローズアップ
D-d-d-da-da fearless! Sensational close-up!
D.D.D. Don't cry やるぜ徹底的にリサーチだ
D.D.D. Don't cry, I'll do it thoroughly.
大嫌い? しょうがない? クズは病気ね バイバイ・バイ
Hate it? Hate it? Scum is a disease. Bye-bye, bye-bye.
権力! 財産! 地位名声!!
Power! Property! Status, prestige!
なんにもないけど裁きたいでしょ?
You want to judge me for nothing, don't you?
だ・だ・だ・だ 大統領になったらね まずは君を捕まえるね
When I'm president... I'll get you first.
濡れたタオルで 洗いざらい吐かせるね
With a wet towel, I'll make you tell me everything.
誰ですか あの女
Who is that woman?
ダメですか そうですか (いやぁ~)
Oh, I see...
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
I won't let the romance scandal get away.
消してあげる
I'll make it disappear.
シル・ヴ・プレプレジデント
Sil v pre-president!
宣誓! 私が大統領になったら
Oath! When I'm president...
ただの仕事の付き合いだよって言う奴は二度と働けなくしてやります
I'll make sure that anyone who says "I'm just a business associate" will never work again.
宣誓! 以下略!
Oath! The rest is abbreviated!
いや向こうが強引でさあっていう男の口にはレジンを流し込んで固めてやります!
If a guy says, "No, he was too pushy...", I'll pour resin into his mouth and harden it!
み・み・み・み 密着 まででドン・ファン気取りスキャンダラス
Close, close, close, close! He's like Don Juan! Scandalous!
ま・ま・ま・末端価格 甲斐性なしのスクーブね
Frivolous price, a scoop with no capability.
愛はない? 理由じゃない 悪くないのね はいはいはい
No love? That's not a reason. Not bad, isn't it? Yes, yes, yes.
軽薄! のうのう! いけしゃしゃあ!! なんにもないとかありえないでしょ?
How can you be nothing? Even if you're president...
だ・だ・だ・だ 大統領になってもね たぶん君は変わらないね
Maybe you won't change.
しらっととぼけて のらりくらりかわすのね
You'll just play it cool and dodge and dodge.
デートですか こんばんわ (うわぁ~)
You have a date? Good evening.
本気ですか そうですか (おらぁ~)
Are you serious?
情熱とは不注意 微熱も消してしまいたい
Passion is carelessness. I'd like to turn off the slight fever, too.
だ・だ・だ・だ 大統領になったらね
When I'm president...
マジで君を捕まえるね
I'll get you for real.
濡れたタオルで 洗いざらい吐かせるね
With a wet towel, I'll make you tell me everything.
どこですか 今あんた 見っけちゃった バレちゃった (おらー!)
Where are you? I've been spotted. I've been spotted.
夜道にはご用心 さよなら代わりに銃声
Beware of the night. Gunshots instead of goodbye.
Watch your step at night, a gunshot instead of goodbye,
シル・ヴ・プレジデント
S'il vous président!
ドキ・ドキ・して Rouge？
Doki-doki and Rouge?
【いきますよ～！】
Here we go!
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！
Not guilty! Not guilty! Innocent pretty girl!
マリン！マリン！マリンは無罪！
Marine! Marine! Marine is not guilty!
やっぱキラキラ もっとクラクラ
Still sparkling, more dizzying,
【ねぇ、言ったよね？】
Hey, you said it, right?
年齢なんて関係ないってさ そういうめんどさいのも含めて愛してくれないって
Age doesn't matter, you said you'd love me
even with all that troublesome stuff!
【ねぇねぇ、言ったよね？言ってない？】ふん、そういうこというんだ。
Hey hey, did you say it? Or not?
Hmph, so that's how it is.
ちなみにこの船では美少女無罪が適用されますけど？
By the way, 'innocent pretty girl'
applies on this ship, you know?
まかせて！魔法で若返り 若返り
Leave it to me! Rejuvenate with magic,
rejuvenate!
ヒミツの素顔はキミだけに
My secret true face is just for you,
【トクベツですよ～！】
It's special, okay?!
Ah… アタシ厄介よ
Ah... I'm a pain.
Ah… 港なんかじゃ
Ah... Not at a port or anything
はしゃげないわ 近頃はね
I can't get hyped up lately, you know.
宝の島にしてほしい気分
I feel like making it an island of treasure.
（出航ー！！） キュートは正義 美少女無罪
(Set sail!!) Cute is justice,
innocent pretty girl!
キミの一番目指してヨーソロー！
Aiming to be your number one,
full speed ahead!
本当は自信ないけど頑張っちゃう
Honestly I lack confidence,
but I'll do my best!
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん 恋する気持ち17歳
Kyu-kyu-kyurun, a 17-year-old girl in love!
0時〈テッペン〉になっちゃうわ オトナの時間
At midnight it turns into adult time,
（やっぱキラキラ もっとクラクラ ド・キ・ド・キ・して Rouge？ まだ早い♡）
(Still sparkling, more dizzying,
doki-doki with Rouge? Too early♡)
だっだっだめですか？ フリル 服着たら （そんなこと、ないよ〈セルフ〉）
No-no-no way? Wearing frilly clothes
(No way, that's not true)
だっだだって魔法少女になってみたい （ギリギリ有罪！？）
N-n-n-no way, I want to become a magical girl!
(Barely guilty!?)
進路はななん星 ちょっぴり足りない積極性？ （結局キミも もっと若い子？）
Course is what star? A little lacking in aggressiveness?
(Ultimately you want a younger girl too?)
なんだってするから 見捨てないでキミたち！（ちょっとイトコ見てみた～い！）
I'll do anything, so don't abandon us guys!
(I wanna take a peek at my cousin!)
Ah…たまにいじけちゃう Ah…それでもいいの？
Ah... sometimes I get sulky.
Ah... is that still okay?
年頃だもん本気にしちゃう
I'm at that age, so I'll take it seriously!
嵐の中も 一緒に行こう？ （出航ー！！）
Even in the storm, shall we go together?
(Set sail!!)
ハートにチャーム 美少女無罪
Charm on the heart, innocent pretty girl!
あれあれどうした？ めんどくさいようなんて言っちゃって かまってくれるキミが好き
What's wrong? Saying things like 'how troublesome',
I love that you pamper me.
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん 優しくしてね17歳
Kyu-kyu-kyurun, treat me nicely,
I'm 17 years old!
突っ込んで経験値 お楽しみChu♡ （やっぱキラキラ もっとクラクラ）
Dive in for experience points, enjoy the Chu♡
(Still sparkling, more dizzying)
ド・キ・ド・キ・して Rouge？ まだ早い♡ 【あぁ、お許しくだた～い！】
Doki-doki with Rouge? Too early♡
[Ah, please forgive meeeee!]
このマリンの…（魅力！魔力！不可抗力！）――“罪な女”ね？
This Marine's... (Charm! Magic! Irresistible!)
—A 'sinful woman', huh?
離さないでつかまっていて 世界の広さ 見せてあげるから！
Don't let go, hold on tight,
I'll show you how big the world is!
（出航ー！！） キュートは正義 美少女無罪
(Set sail!!) Cute is justice,
innocent pretty girl!
キミの一番目指してヨーソロー！
Aiming to be your number one,
full speed ahead!
冗談も大好きだけど真剣よ （Ahoy!!）
I love jokes too, but I'm serious!
(Ahoy!!)
きゅっ きゅっ きゅるん 恋する気持ち17歳
Kyu-kyu-kyurun, a 17-year-old girl in love!
0時〈テッペン〉になっちゃうわ オトナの時間
At midnight it turns into adult time,
（やっぱキラキラ もっとクラクラ ド・キ・ド・キ・して Rouge？ まだ早い♡）
(Still sparkling, more dizzying,
doki-doki with Rouge? Too early♡)
無罪！無罪！美少女無罪！
Not guilty! Not guilty! Innocent pretty girl!
マリン！マリン！マリンは無罪！
Marine! Marine! Marine is not guilty!
やっぱキラキラ もっとクラクラ
Still sparkling, more dizzying,
【マリンじゃなくて、マリン船長だろぅん！？】
[Not just Marine, Captain Marine, right?!]
ピーマールさまが来てくれました！
P Maru-sama came to join us!
わあ～来てくれてありがとうございます！
Wow~ Thank you so much for coming!
え、実はマリン、めっちゃくちゃ好きなんです、ピーマールさまが！
Um, actually Marine, I like you so, so much, P Maru-sama!
やったーーー！！！やったーーー！！！
Yayyy!!! Yayyy!!!
ところで、Pマールさま、今日はね、マリンの誕生日なんです。
By the way, P Maru-sama, today is Marine's birthday.
え！おめでとう！
Eh! Happy birthday!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
え、本当は何歳？
Eh, how old are you really?
えー、まあ、17から30の間を可変式にこう…行ったり来たりしてまーす。
Um, well, I sort of... fluctuate back and forth between 17 and 30!
ぼくも！ぼくも！いっしょいっしょ！
Me too! Me too! Same here!
ぼくもじゃねぇよ！
Not you too!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ということでね、ちょっとやっぱPマール様と歌うならと思ってね、
So, since I thought if I'm singing with P-maru-sama,
もうみんな大好きな「シルブプレジデント」と...
everyone's favorite "C'est la vie President"—
言いづらい！
it's a tongue-twister!
「シルブプレジデント」歌わせてもらいましたけど。
We got to sing "C'est la vie President"!
いやめちゃくちゃ最高！
It was amazing!
いやめちゃくちゃビショパピ大好きだから！
We love "C'est la vie President" so much!
えー嬉しい！
Yay, I'm so happy!
え、さっきのちょっとプチ裏話は話してもいいやつですか？
Can we talk about the behind-the-scenes story just now?
あ、全然いいよ！
Yeah, totally fine!
なんかPマール様、なんとビショパピ歌ってみたをね、出そうとしてたらしいくて。
Apparently, P-maru-sama was planning to release a cover of it.
そう！
That's right!
出そうかな！
I was thinking of releasing it!
いやでもいいか、今更...
But wait, is it too late now...
いや今更、今更！いや遅くないか？
No, it's not too late! Or is it?
遅いけど、そうでもちょうど歌おうと思ってた時に...
It's late, but just when I was thinking of singing it,
マリンが声かけしてくれたみたいで、そう、ちょうどよくね！
Marine reached out to me, so the timing was just right!
いや本当ちょうどよかったね！
Yeah, the timing was perfect!
いやこちらこそありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
いやPマール様ってさ、いきなり指差ししてるみたいになってるけど、これ呼び方大丈夫そ？
You're pointing right at me—is this way of addressing you okay?
いやいいよ、いいよ！
Yeah, it's totally fine!
あ、いいっすか？
Oh, really?
え、じゃあなんて呼ぼう？マリンは？
Then what should I call you? Marine?
え、待って。これ... マリー?
Wait. This... Mari?
マリーちゃん？
Mari-chan?
これ初絡み！初絡み！
This is our first time interacting!
そうなの！
That's right!
実は... そうなの！
Actually... that's right!
え、なんでも、なんかPマールに、マリンでも... え、船長かな？
Can I call you P-maru, Marine, or... Captain?
あ、船長！船長で！
Ah, Captain! Call me Captain!
Pマール様って、でも普段Pちゃんとか呼ばれてますよね？
But normally people call you P-chan, right?
あ、呼ばれてるけど、まだちょっと仲良くなりたいから...
Yeah, but since we want to get closer...
もうちょっと仲良くなりたい！
I want us to get closer!
で、こよぴとかともね、コラボしてましたよね？
And you collaborated with Koyori-chan too, right?
え、こよぴのことはなんて呼んでるの？
What do you call Koyori-chan?
こよぴちゃん！
Koyori-chan!
あ、こよぴちゃん！
Ah, Koyori-chan!
え、仲いい？
Are you close?
え、仲いいと思ってけど、こよぴちゃんはどうかわからない。
I thought we were close, but I don't know about Koyori-chan.
いや思ってる、思ってる！こよぴちゃんありがとう！
No, she thinks so too! Thanks, Koyori-chan!
こよぴちゃんありがとう！
Thanks, Koyori-chan!
いきなり、ちょっと待って、ヨソジしないですぐ...
Wait, don't keep your distance right away...
マリンのことだけ見て！
Look only at Marine!
そうだ、そうだ、そうだよね！
That's right, exactly!
でかい！
It's huge!
でか... え、何が？何が？
Huge... wait, what? What is?
え、何これ？これこれこれ！
Eh, what's this? This, this, this!
でかい！ここ、ここ、ここ！
Huge! Right here, here, here!
え、僕も、僕も、僕も！
Eh, me too, me too, me too!
あ、でもなんか、これくらいだよね？
But well, it's about this much, right?
は？
Huh?
おい！
Hey!
こんな感じだよね？
Something like this, right?
いい、いい、いい！
Good, good, good!
ありがとう！こういうのがいいんだよ！
Thank you! This is what's good!
結局なんだかんだね！
At the end of the day!
でかいし、ちっちゃい！
Big and small!
あ、そうなの！ちっちゃいんです、意外と！
Ah, that's right! It's surprisingly small!
え、でもピーちゃんもかわいい！
But P-chan is cute too!
ありがとう！こんなちっちゃいんだ！
Thank you! It's so small!
ええ！顔はでかい！
Eh! Your face is big!
か、顔はでかい、か！
Your face is big, huh!
やめなさい！顔は！
Stop it! Your face!
顔でかい、胸でかい、背ちっちゃい！
Face is big, chest is big, height is small!
あ、そっか。顔で... お前もでかいじゃん！
Ah, right. Your face... You're big too!
確かに！確かに！顔は！
True! True! Your face!
よかった,でも同じくらいの顔のデカさだから！
Well, our face sizes are about the same, so that's good!
バランスいいな！バラシいい！
Good balance! Great balance!
また一緒に歌いたいな！
I want to sing together again!
わ、僕も！また一緒に歌おう！もっと仲良くなろうね！
Me too, me too! Let's sing together again! Let's get closer!
いっちゃん、何しましょう？
P-icchan, what should we do?
マリン先輩！
Marine-senpai!
距離が！距離がすごいある！
The distance! There's a huge distance!
先輩じゃなかった、船長！
I wasn't Marine-senpai, Captain!
はい、船長ね。よりしてで、ため口でいいので。ありがとうございます！
Right, Captain. Feel free to use casual speech. Thank you!
さあ、もうね、ライブも終盤となっておりますので、
Now, the live stream is reaching its climax,
まだまだラストスパートも盛り上がっていきたいと思います！
So we want to get even more hyped for the final stretch!
それではいきましょう！
Let's go!
チューコー！
Chu-ko!
おお！すごい！
Wow, awesome!
はい、まー、ありがとうございます！
Yes, thank you so much!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
あ、だんだんきえる、だんだんきえる...
Ah, slowly disappearing...
ゴキゲンな蝶になって きらめく風に乗って
I'll become a happy butterfly, and ride the winds that take me up high
今すぐ キミに会いに行こう
I'll be there soon, by your side
余計な事なんて 忘れた方がマシさ
It's better to forget unnecessary things
これ以上 シャレてる時間はない
There's no more time to be fooling around
何が WOW WOW〜 この空に届くのだろう
I wanna know, what will reach this sky?
だけど WOW WOW〜 明日の予定もわからない
Don't even know, what tomorrow's schedule holds
無限大な夢のあとの 何もない世の中じゃ
After the dream without any end, in this world without nothing in it
そうさ愛しい 想いも負けそうになるけど
It seems like all of our dreams, will lose all of its light...
Stayしがちなイメージだらけの 頼りない翼でも きっと飛べるさ On My Love
Even with these wavering wings, I'm sure that we can both fly, on my love.
ウカレタ蝶になって 一途な風に乗って
I'll become a cheerful butterfly, and ride the winds with earnest feelings
どこまでも キミに会いに行こう
I'll come to see you, wherever you might be
曖昧な言葉って 意外に便利だって
Words that are surprisingly handy, ambiguously convenient
叫んで ヒットソング聴きながら
Shouting while listening to a hit song
何が WOW WOW この街に響くのだろう
What is it, WOW WOW, that will echo through this town?
だけど WOW WOW 期待してても仕方ない
But, WOW WOW, there's no use anticipating
無限大な夢のあとの やるせない世の中じゃ
After an endless dream, in this miserable world,
そうさ常識 はずれも悪くはないかな
That's right, maybe not using common sense isn't so bad after all
Stayしそうなイメージを染めた ぎこちない翼でも
Even with these awkward wings, dyed with images that seem to stay,
きっと飛べるさ On My Love
I'm sure we can fly, On My Love
無限大な夢のあとの 何もない世の中じゃ
After an endless dream, in this world of nothingness,
そうさ愛しい 想いも負けそうになるけど
That's right, even if our beloved dreams feel like they're going to lose,
Stayしちなイメージだらけの 頼ない翼でも
Even with unreliable wings, full of images that tend to stay,
きっと飛べるさ
I'm sure we can fly
Oh Yeah～
Oh Yeah~
無限大な夢のあとの やるせない世の中じゃ
After an endless dream, in this miserable world,
そうさ常識 はずれも悪くはないかな
That's right, maybe not using common sense isn't so bad after all
Stayしそうなイメージを染めた ぎこちない翼でも きっと飛べるさ
Even with these awkward wings, dyed with images that seem to stay, I'm sure we can fly
On My Love
私のもの そう私のもの 千の黄金
Mine, yes, my very own, a thousand pieces of gold
数百年の財宝 この船に眠る
Centuries of treasure sleep within this ship
私のもの そう私のもの 奪ってみろ
Mine, yes, my very own, try and take it
命の証を 貴方の求める全てを
The proof of life, everything you desire
輝きは 燻んで 錆びついて
The radiance tarnishes and rusts
それでも 泥舟にしがみつくなら 泡沫と共に沈め
Even so, if you cling to a sinking ship, sink away with the foam
黒い帆に 隠れる “極上の海賊の秘宝” 掴んで笑う
Hidden by black sails, grab the "supreme pirate treasure" and laugh
このあと プレミア公開
[On-screen: Shortly, Premiere Screening]
全国流通 1stアルバム発売決定！
[Album Announcement: 1st Nationwide Album Release!]
Ahoy!! キミたちみんなパイレーツ♡
[Album Title: Ahoy!! You're All Pirates♡]
Ahoy!! 我ら宝海団☆
[Track: Ahoy!! We Are the Houshou Marine Pirates☆]
Unison
[Track: Unison]
Happiness World
[Track: Happiness World]
マリン出航!!
[Track: Marine, Set Sail!!]
I'm Your Treasure Box
[Track: I'm Your Treasure Box]
美少女無罪♡パイレーツ
[Track: Bishoujo Muzai♡Pirates]
SHINKIRO
[Track: SHINKIRO]
ピパポ☆ピパプ
[Track: Pipapo☆Pipapu]
///
[Track: ///]
幽霊船戦
[Track: Dead Ma'am's Chest]
さらに！アルバムに向けて豪華クリエイター陣が書き下ろした新曲4曲を収録！
[Note: Featuring 4 new songs written by top creators!]
私のもの そう私のもの 千の黄金
Mine, yes, my very own, a thousand pieces of gold
数百年の財宝 この船に眠る
Centuries of treasure sleep within this ship
古びた伝説は 呪われた幽霊船に
Ancient legends whisper of a cursed ghost ship,
続く夜の潮路
upon the endless, nocturnal tides.
そこに富が残る 海賊の夢があるのなら
If there are pirate dreams of wealth left behind,
頂くしかないでしょ？
surely you have to claim them, right?
「無謀な赤よ 若き盗人よ」
"Foolish red thing, reckless young thief,"
「命をもって 後悔に代えさせてやろう」
"pay for your regrets with your life."
止まない雨の弾丸で 駆ける鼓動
Amidst endless raindrops and pounding heartbeats...
美しいほど この瞳焦がす 生命の炎 ガネットの色彩 攫う宝石なのだから
If you're after those stunning, burning-hot garnet gems...
攫う宝石なのだから
try and steal them from me!
私のもの そう私のもの 奪ってみろ
They're mine, truly mine! Try and snatch them,
命の証を 貴方の求める全てを
and prove your very life for all you desire!
輝きはくすんで 錆びついて
Even if the brilliance fades and rusts away,
それでも 泥舟にしがみつくなら
still, if you cling to a sinking ship,
泡沫と共に沈め
sink down into the bubbles together!
黒い帆に隠れる
Hidden by black sails,
“極上の海賊の秘宝”
"the ultimate pirate treasure,"
掴んで笑う
grab it and laugh!
満月の金銀珠玉
The silver and gold jewels of the full moon,
七つの海の宝玉に
the treasures of the seven seas...
「集る虫ども」
"You swarming pests,"
こそり富を狙う 愚か者に思い知らず
foolish wretches blindly chasing stolen riches,
相応しい持ち主を
find the masters you deserve!
船に宿る 黒い魂の群れ
Swarms of dark souls lingering in the ship,
影の底で 忍び寄る絶望の渦
a vortex of despair lurking in the depths of shadows,
まるで蓋の閉じた箱
like a sealed box.
手放しちゃえば 諦めちゃえば 悪夢の中から逃げられるのに
Let go, give up—even though you could escape this nightmare,
まだ掴んでる 欲望が重いから
you're still clinging on because your desires are too heavy!
わたしのもの そうわたしのもの
It's mine, yes, it's mine!
自分自身を信じ込ませて 縛って
I brainwashed and bound myself tight,
縛り付けてたって気付いた
only to realize I was the one who tied the knot!
呪いの出口 永久の夜の海域
The exit from the curse, the eternal sea of night—
目を覚まして 貴方の悪夢から
wake up from your nightmare,
連れ出す現舟よ 出航して
take out the phantom ship and set sail!
私のもの まだ私のもの 純紅のバラ
It's mine, still mine—a deep crimson rose.
朽ち果てたとしても 枯れない魂までは
Even if it withers away, until my soul refuses to fade,
万の幽珠 永遠の美貌
ten thousand phantom pearls, an eternal beauty—
そんな幻 どうだっていいでしょう
such an illusion is fine just as it is!
手放す 決意はついたかい
Have you made up your mind to let go?
さあ行こう 夜明けに舵を向けて
Now let's go, turn the helm toward the dawn,
日暮を宿した船 希望だけ残して航く
sailing on with only the phantom ship and our hopes,
他にはもういらないから
because there's nothing else I need anymore!
私のもの そう私のもの
Mine, yes, mine alone...
千の黄金
A thousand pieces of gold.
数百年の財宝 この船に眠る
Centuries of treasure sleeping in this ship.
古びた伝説は 呪われた幽霊船に
The ancient legend speaks of a cursed ghost ship,
続く夜の潮路 そこに富が残る
and the endless night tide where wealth remains.
海賊の夢がある ならば
If you have a pirate's dream,
頂くしかないでしょ？
you must claim the very top!
「無謀な赤よ 若き盗人よ」
"Foolish redheads, young thieves,"
「命をもっで 後悔に代えさせてやろう」
"Pay for your regrets with your very lives."
止まない雨の弾丸で
Amidst the relentless rain of bullets...
(駆ける心動 まだこの足走れるはず)
(Racing heartbeats, these feet must still be able to run!)
美しいほど この瞳焦がす 生命の炎
So breathtaking, this blinding spark of life,
ガーネットの色彩
the colors of the garnet.
捗る 宝石なのかな
If you're grasping for precious gems...
(ガーネットの色彩 貴方にはない)
(The colors of the garnet are unlike anything you have.)